EDMUND LAI edmundlaicg.com

Profile

Personal

An affable, intuitive and selfmotivated CG animator / artist with a background in interaction design. His goal is to produce work that reaches out to people on a deeper level.

Waterloo, Ontario Conceptual Flash Designer (Co-op)

BlackBerry (formerly Research in Motion)

Design Work Experience

Jan. 2010 - Sept. 2010

Responsibilities

Designed and developed interactive Flash storyboards, posters and presentations to showcase and demonstrate conceptual products, which facilitated the implementation of new functions into future devices

Technical

CG Software

Maya / XSI / Mudbox / ZBrush

CG Skills

Animation / Modelling / Lighting / Materials

Miscellaneous

Adobe Creative Suite / Web development / UX design / OSX / Windows

IBM Canada Ltd.

Burnaby, British Columbia Interactive Media Designer (Co-op) Sept. 2008 - Apr. 2009

Responsibilities

Developed and maintained both internal company and external client Websites following strict standards, which ensured that pages are cross-browser compliant and accessible to screen readers

Education

Capilano University

North Vancouver, British Columbia

Certificates

- ▶ Digital Animation
- ▶ Computer Animation and Visual Effects (summer intensive)

Simon Fraser University

Burnaby, British Columbia

Degrees

- ▶ B.A. under Interactive Arts and Technology in Media Arts
- ▶ B.B.A. in Marketing

Contact Info

Location

Vancouver, BC, Canada (Killarney area)

Contact

Phone F-mail

1-778-855-8092 edmundl@gmail.com

Portfolio

edmundlaicg.com

More About Me

Character

Open-minded / task-oriented / empathetic / genuine

Languages

Fluent Verbally fluent English Cantonese

Other Work Experience

Hi-def Ninja

Online

Bluraysteelbooks.com News Writer Oct. 2011 - Jun. 2012

Starbucks

Vancouver, British Columbia Barista

Aug. 2006 - Dec. 2009

Reference

Available upon request